foreverliving.com 2019-04-08

# Last Updated: October 23, 2018

                                   Forever Living Products Privacy Notice
                                             Last Updated: October 23, 2018
Table of Contents
  Who We Are ............................................................................................................................................. 1
  Information You May Provide Us ........................................................................................................... 1
  Other Information We May Collect About You ...................................................................................... 2
  Cookies ..................................................................................................................................................... 3
  Disclosure of Your Information .............................................................................................................. 3
  Where We Store Your Personal Information ........................................................................................ 4
  Access, Control, and Your Rights ............................................................................................................ 4
  Children’s Online Information Policy..................................................................................................... 5
  Contact Us ................................................................................................................................................ 5
  Changes to Our Privacy Notice ............................................................................................................... 5
LEGAL NOTICE: By visiting any of the Forever Living Products (hereinafter “FLP”) family of
websites that contain this Privacy Notice, you are accepting and consenting in full to the
practices described in this Privacy Notice.
Who We Are
FLP, founded in 1978 with its headquarters in Scottsdale, Arizona, is the largest grower,
manufacturer, and distributor of Aloe Vera in the world. FLP, operating in more than 150
countries, is vertically integrated, controlling everything from the fields, to the factory, to
research and development, to packaging, shipping, and distribution. FLP’s exclusive line
products has helped people around the world look better and feel better. For additional
information about FLP, please visit: http://www.foreverliving.com.
Please read the following Privacy Notice carefully to understand our views and practices
regarding your personal information and how we will treat your personal information.
Information You May Provide Us
We may collect and process the following information about you that you provide to us so
that we can provide the best possible experience when you use our services. Personal
information that you provide us may include the following:
•   Full Name
•   Address(es)
•   Phone Numbers
•   E-mail Address(es)
•   Date of Birth
•   Payment Information (i.e., Credit Card Information)
•   Bank Account Information
•   Social Security Number/Tax ID
•   Personal Description
•   Signature(s)
October 23, 2018                                            Privacy Notice 1.0                                                                        Page 1

                         Forever Living Products Privacy Notice
•   Spouses Name
•   Spouses Information
•   Customer Care Phone Call Recording
•   Photograph
•   Other Data Collected That Could Directly or Indirectly Identify You
Other personal information and documents containing personal information may be
collected from time to time for business purposes, for example, to process bonuses.
This category of information is information you provide us by performing certain tasks:
•   Applying to join FLP as a Forever Business Owner (“FBO”) from an FLP website;
•   Purchasing products or submitting an order from an FLP website;
•   Entering a competition, promotion, or survey;
•   Participating in any interactive aspects of an FLP website by engaging in forums or
    submitting comments about services and/or products;
•   Submitting an information request from an FLP website;
•   Reporting a problem with an FLP website; or
•   Consenting to receive marketing material.
FLP takes considerable pride in adhering to applicable federal and state laws and will not
share your personal information with any outside companies or vendors except for the
facilitation of a business-related process or financial transactions on your behalf.
For personal information provided to a third party, this Privacy Notice applies to your
personal information only once we receive the personal information.
Other Information We May Collect About You
During each of your visits to our FLP websites, we may collect the following information:
•   Technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your
    computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone
    setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform;
•   Information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL),
    clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time), products you viewed
    or searched for page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages,
    page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), methods used
    to browse away from the page, any phone number used to call our customer service
    number, and any e-mail address used to contact us.
Information We Receive From Other Sources
We may work closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-
contractors in technical, payment, and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics
providers, search information providers) and may receive information about you from these
October 23, 2018                      Privacy Notice 1.0                               Page 2

                          Forever Living Products Privacy Notice
providers. We will notify you when we receive information about you from these providers
and the purposes for which we intend to use that information.
Cookies
Cookies are small pieces of data sent from a website and stored on the user’s computer by
the user's web browser while the user is browsing to remember information (such as items
added in the shopping cart in an online store) or to record the user's browsing activity.
The “Help” feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from
accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie,
or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used
by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the
website of its manufacturer.
Because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of FLP’s essential features, we
recommend that you leave them turned on.
Disclosure of Your Information
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the
business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described below and
with subsidiaries. You agree that we have the right to disclose your personal information as
needed to conduct our business activities according to the following, and in the following,
circumstances:
•   Internal Disclosure: We necessarily require storage and disclosure of your information
    within our various business units on an as-needed basis in order to effectively conduct
    our legitimate business activities.
•   Third-Party Service Providers: We employ other companies and individuals to
    perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include sending postal mail and e-mail,
    removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing
    marketing assistance, providing search results and links, processing credit card
    payments, and providing customer service. These providers have access to personal
    information needed to perform their functions in accordance with contractual
    obligations but may not use it for other purposes.
•   Promotional Offers: FLP never sells, trades, or leases your personal information to an
    unrelated third party without your express consent. From time to time, FLP may send
    offers and promotional material to you to (1) provide you with information about other
    goods and services that FLP offers that are similar to those that you have purchased and
    inquired about, or (2) to notify you about changes to our goods and services. Individuals
    are free to opt-out of these promotional offers at any time on the website, e-mail
    transmittal, or by contacting our Home Office by telephone at 1-888-440-ALOE (2563).
 •   Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy
     properties, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information
October 23, 2018                       Privacy Notice 1.0                                Page 3

                          Forever Living Products Privacy Notice
     generally is one of the transferred and/or shared business assets but remains subject to
     the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the customer
     consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that FLP assets are acquired, customer
     information may be one of the transferred assets.
 •   Protection of FLP and Others: We release account and other personal information
     when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply
     our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of
     FLP, our customers, or others. This may include exchanging information with other
     companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously,
     however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing
     personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in
     violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.
 •   With Your Consent: Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when
     information about you might be sent to other third parties, and you will have an
     opportunity to choose not to share the information.
Where We Store Your Personal Information
The information that we collect from you will be transferred to, and stored at, a destination
in the United States, outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It will also be processed
by staff operating outside the EEA who are employed by one or more of our FLP entities. This
includes staff engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your orders, the processing
of your payment details, and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal
information, you agree to its transfer, storing, or processing. We will take all steps reasonably
necessary to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this
Privacy Notice.
All information you provide to us is stored on secure servers. We maintain a wide variety of
programs and security and controls to protect your information. Any payment transactions
will be encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. We follow the Payment Card
Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) when handling credit card data. Where we have
given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts
of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to
share a password with anyone. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure.
Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the
security of your information transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk.
Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features
to try to prevent unauthorized access.
Access, Control, and Your Rights
If you created an account during the registration process, you can view, update, and delete
certain information about yourself and your interactions with FLP. If you have an order
October 23, 2018                       Privacy Notice 1.0                                  Page 4

                         Forever Living Products Privacy Notice
confirmation number, you may be able to change and update your order. If you cannot access
or update your information yourself, you can always contact FLP for assistance.
If you wish to exercise any of your rights as a data subject or discuss your rights, please let
us know using any of the contact information in the introduction to this Privacy Notice. We
may ask you to provide valid form of identification for verification purposes. Your rights are
as follows:
•   The right to access the information we hold about you.
•   The right to rectification, portability, erasure, restriction, objection.
•   The right to withdraw consent at any time.
•   The right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.
•   The right to know the consequences of your failure to provide necessary information.
•   The right to not be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing.
If you make a request to delete your personal information and that information is necessary
for the products or services you have purchased, the request will be honored only to the
extent it is no longer necessary for any services purchased or required for our legitimate
business purposes or legal or contractual record keeping requirements.
Children’s Online Information Policy
FLP does not intend for our web sites to be used by anyone under the age of 18. We do not
knowingly market to, or collect information from, anyone who may be under the age of 18;
and none of our data accumulating web pages (including, but not limited to, registration,
ordering, marketing opt-ins, and contact requests) are intended, or should be used by,
anyone under the age of 18.
Contact Us
If you have any questions, concerns, or complaints about our Privacy Notice, you may contact
us at privacy@foreverliving.com.
Changes to Our Privacy Notice
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Notice at any time. If we decide to change our
Privacy Notice, we will post those changes to this Privacy Notice and any other places we
deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and
under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we make material changes to this Privacy
Notice, we will notify you here, by e-mail, or by means of a notice on our home page.
October 23, 2018                       Privacy Notice 1.0                               Page 5
